A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of XX, XX-XX (bulk 2014-2017)
Library of Virginia
- Series V. Legislative Files, 2014-2018., Extent: X cubic feet (X box). (Box XX)
  - Legislative proposals - Statements of need, 2016.
  - Legislative proposals - ABC, 2016.
  - Legislative proposals - DOC, 2016.
  - Legislative proposals - DCJS, 2016.
  - Legislative proposals - VDEM, 2016.
  - Legislative proposals - DFP, 2016.
  - Legislative proposals - DJJ, 2016.
  - Legislative proposals - DMA, 2016.
  - Legislative proposals - VSP, 2016.
  - Mental health legislation, 2016.
  - Legislation - 2017 General Assembly Session
    - Driver's licenses, 2017.
    - Governor - Public Safety bills, 2017.
    - Gun legislation, 2017.
    - HB 1924 Suspension, 2017.
    - Initial discussions, 2017.
    - Legislative proposals, 2017.
    - Legislative proposals - Statements of need, 2017.
    - Legislative proposals - Statements of need, 2017.
    - Legislative proposals - ABC, 2017.
    - Legislative proposals - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice, 2017.
    - Legislative proposals - DOC, 2017.
    - Legislative proposals - DOC / Board, 2017.
    - Legislative proposals - DCJS, 2017.
    - Legislative proposals - DFS, 2017.
    - Legislative proposals - DJJ, 2017.
    - Legislative proposals - Opioid bills, 2017.
    - Veto, 2017.
  - Legislation - 2018 General Assembly Session
    - Legislation, 2018.
    - Legislative proposals - ABC, 2018.
    - Legislative proposals - DOC, 2018.
    - Legislative proposals - DCJS, 2018.
    - Legislative proposals - VDEM, 2018.
    - Legislative proposals - DFP, 2018.
    - Legislative proposals - DFS, 2018.
    - Legislative proposals - DJJ, 2018.
    - Legislative proposals - DMA, 2018.
    - Legislative proposals - VSP, 2018.
- Series VI. Special Projects and Studies, XX., Extent: X cubic feet (X boxes). (Box X)
  The Special Projects and Studies series is housed in X boxes and is arranged alphabetically. This series documents the Secretary of Public Safety's interaction with and oversight of various projects and studies. This series may include, but is not limited to, projects and studies associated with Governor's initiatives, issues, and topics.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice, 2016-2017.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Advisory Group meetings, 2016-2017.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Alternate Transportation Workgroup, 2017 Oct 10.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Background and organization, 2015-2017.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Behavioral and mental health care in jails, 2016-2017.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Budget review, 2016-2017.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Executive Committee, 2016 May 9.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Executive Committee, 2016 June 6.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Executive Committee, 2016 July 5.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Executive Committee, 2016 Sept 16.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Executive Committee, 2016 Oct 6.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Executive Committee, 2016 Nov 7.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Executive Committee, 2016 Dec 5.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Executive Committee, 2017 Feb 7.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Executive Committee, 2017 Mar 6.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Executive Committee, 2017 Apr 3.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Executive Committee, 2017 May 15.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Governor's Access Plan (GAP) for the Seriously Mentally Ill / Medicare Waiver Program, 2016.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Jail Diversion Programs, 2016.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Joint Subcommittee to Study Mental Health Services, 2017.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Joint Subcommittee to Study Mental Health Services - Workgroup 2, Criminal Justice Diversion, 2017 June 20.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Peumansend Creek Regional Jail, 2016.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Subcommittee meeting, 2016 May 20.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Talking points, 2016.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Technology, Data, and Information Sharing Action Committee, 2016 Sept 9.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Technology, Data, and Information Sharing Action Committee, 2016 Dec 20.
  - Center for Behavioral Health and Justice - Transitioning youth, 2017.
  - Children's Cabinet - Meetings, 2014.
  - Children's Cabinet - Meeting, 2014 Apr 21.
  - Children's Cabinet - Meeting, 2015 May 14.
  - Children's Cabinet - Meeting, 2015 June 20.
  - Children's Cabinet - Staff Workgroup, 2016 Mar 2.
  - Children's Cabinet - Meeting, 2016 Mar 21.
  - Children's Cabinet - Retreat, 2016 May 2.
  - Children's Cabinet - Retreat Follow-up Session, 2016 May 19.
  - Children's Cabinet - Staff Workgroup, 2016 June 2.
  - Children's Cabinet - Staff Workgroup, 2016 June 30.
  - Children's Cabinet - Meeting, 2016 June 30.
  - Children's Cabinet - Staff Workgroup, 2016 Aug 3.
  - Children's Cabinet - Meeting, 2016 Aug 15.
  - Children's Cabinet - Staff Workgroup, 2016 Nov 9.
  - Children's Cabinet - Meeting, 2016 Nov 21.
  - Children's Cabinet - Meeting, 2016 Dec 19.
  - Children's Cabinet - Meeting, 2017 Mar 28.
  - Children's Cabinet - Meeting, 2017 Apr 17.
  - Children's Cabinet - Retreat, 2017 May 23.
  - Children's Cabinet - Staff Workgroup, 2017 June 7.
  - Children's Cabinet - Staff Workgroup, 2017 Aug 3.
  - Children's Cabinet - Meeting, 2017 Aug 21.
  - Children's Cabinet - Virginia School/Law Enforcement Partnership, 2017.
  - Children's Cabinet - Adverse childhood experiences, undated.
  - Children's Cabinet - Annual Report (2015-2016), 2016 Oct.
  - Children's Cabinet - Classrooms, Not Courtrooms, 2015-2016.
  - Climate Change and Resiliency Update Commission - Meeting, 2015 Aug 28.
  - Combating Campus Sexual Violence, Task Force on, 2014-2015.
  - Combating Campus Sexual Violence, Task Force on - Meeting, 2014 Oct 9.
  - Combating Campus Sexual Violence, Task Force on - Report and Final Recommendations to the Governor, 2015 May 28.
  - Cyber Security - General, 201.
  - Cyber Security - Cybersecurity Advisory Board, 2014 Jan 6.
  - Cyber Security - Cyber Security Commission, 2015.
  - Cyber Security - Cyber Crime Working Group, 2014 Sept 12.
  - Cyber Security - Cyber Response Working Group, 2017 Nov 28.
  - Homelessness - Governor's Coordinating Council on Homelessness, 2014 Oct 3.
  - Homelessness - Governor's Coordinating Council on Homelessness, 2015 Apr 8.
  - Homelessness - Homeless Outcomes Coordinating Council, 2014 Mar 20.
  - Homelessness - Homeless Outcomes Coordinating Council, 2014 June 11.
  - Immediate Sanction Probation Pilot Project, 2014.
  - Immediate Sanction Probation Pilot Project - Briefing, 2012-2014.
  - Improving Mental Health Services and Crisis Response, Governor's Task Force on - Crisis Response Workgroup, 2014 Jan 24.
  - Improving Mental Health Services and Crisis Response, Governor's Task Force on - Crisis Response Workgroup, 2014 Mar 19.
  - Juvenile Correctional Centers, Task Force on, 2016.
  - Juvenile Correctional Centers, Task Force on - Correspondence, 2016.
  - Juvenile Correctional Centers, Task Force on - Interim Report, 2016.
  - Juvenile Correctional Centers, Task Force on - Meeting, 2016 May 12.
  - Juvenile Correctional Centers, Task Force on - Meeting, 2016 May 31.
  - Juvenile Correctional Centers, Task Force on -, 2016 June 14.
  - Juvenile Correctional Centers, Task Force on - Meeting, 2016 Aug 23.
  - National Governors Association - Best Practices Learning Lab (Opioids), 2016-2017.
  - National Governors Association - Best Practices Learning Lab (Opioids), 2017.
  - National Governors Association - Council of Governors, 2016 July 14.
  - National Governors Association - Governor's Criminal Justice Policy Advisors, 2014.
  - National Governors Association - Governor's Guide to Homeland Security, 2010.
  - National Governors Association - Governor's Homeland Security Advisors Council, 2014 June 9-11.
  - National Governors Association - Governor's Homeland Security Advisors Council, 2015 Aug 17-19.
  - National Governors Association - Homeland Security and Public Safety Committee, 2015.
  - National Governors Association - National Criminal Justice Reform Project, 2016 May 24.
  - National Governors Association - Prescription Drug Abuse Reduction Strategy, 2014.
  - National Governors Association - Summit on State Cyber Security, 2015 Mar 30-31.
  - National Governors Association - Survey responses, undated.
  - Offender Population Forecasting - Liaison Workgroup, 2016 Sept 1.
  - Offender Population Forecasting - Liaison Workgroup, 2016 Sept 20.
  - Offender Population Forecasting - Policy Advisory Committee, 2015 Sept-Oct.
  - Offender Population Forecasting - Policy Advisory Committee, 2015 Oct 2.
  - Offender Population Forecasting - Policy Committee, 2016 Sept 7.
  - Offender Population Forecasting - Policy Committee, 2016 Sept 28.
  - Opioids - Governor's Executive Leadership Team on Opioid Abuse and Addiction, 2016-2017.
  - Opioids - Governor's Executive Leadership Team on Opioid Abuse and Addiction, 2016 Oct 7.
  - Opioids - Governor's Executive Leadership Team on Opioid Abuse and Addiction, 2016 Dec 12.
  - Opioids - Governor's Executive Leadership Team on Opioid Abuse and Addiction, 2017 Mar 14.
  - Opioids - Governor's Executive Leadership Team on Opioid Abuse and Addiction, 2017 Apr 6.
  - Opioids - Governor's Executive Leadership Team on Opioid Abuse and Addiction, 2017 Apr 26.
  - Opioids - Governor's Executive Leadership Team on Opioid Abuse and Addiction, 2017 June 1.
  - Opioids - Governor's Executive Leadership Team on Opioid Abuse and Addiction, 2017 July 20.
  - Opioids - Governor's Executive Leadership Team on Opioid Abuse and Addiction, 2017 Aug 3.
  - Opioids - Governor's Executive Leadership Team on Opioid Abuse and Addiction, 2017 Aug 10.
  - Opioids - Governor's Executive Leadership Team on Opioid Abuse and Addiction, 2017 Aug 17.
  - Opioids - Governor's Executive Leadership Team on Opioid Abuse and Addiction, 2017 Aug 23.
  - Opioids - Governor's Executive Leadership Team on Opioid Abuse and Addiction, 2017 Oct 12.
  - Opioids - Governor's Task Force on Opioid and Heroin Abuse - Stakeholders meeting, 2016 May 4.
  - Opioids - Governor's Task Force on Opioid and Heroin Abuse - Stakeholders meeting, 2016 Nov 8.
  - Opioids - Governor's Task Force on Opioid and Heroin Abuse - Stakeholders meeting, 2017 June 21.
  - Opioids - Governor's Task Force on Opioid and Heroin Abuse - Stakeholders meeting, 2017 Oct 18.
  - Opioids - Opioid Executive Workgroup, 2016 Aug 17.
  - Opioids - Governor's Task Force on Prescription Drug and Heroin Abuse, 2014 Dec 16.
  - Opioids - Governor's Task Force on Prescription Drug and Heroin Abuse, 2015 Mar 19.
  - Opioids - Governor's Task Force on Prescription Drug and Heroin Abuse, 2015 May 2.
  - Opioids - Governor's Task Force on Prescription Drug and Heroin Abuse (Virginia Drug Treatment Courts), 2015 June 16.
  - Opioids - Governor's Task Force on Prescription Drug and Heroin Abuse, 2015 Spet 21.
  - Opioids - Governor's Task Force on Prescription Drug and Heroin Abuse - Opioid bill signing, undated.
  - Opioids - Governor's Task Force on Prescription Drug and Heroin Abuse - Talking points, 2014.
  - Physical Evidence Recovery Kit Workgroup, 2015 Sept 17.
  - Physical Evidence Recovery Kit Workgroup, 2015 Oct 23.
  - Physical Evidence Recovery Kit Workgroup, 2015 Nov 9.
  - Physical Evidence Recovery Kit Workgroup, 2016 Jan 13.
  - Public Safety Preparedness and Response to Civil Unrest, Governor's Task Force on, 2017 Oct 2.
  - Public Safety Preparedness and Response to Civil Unrest, Governor's Task Force on - Local Permitting Guidance Document, 2017 Nov.
  - Railroad Safety and Security Task Force - Meetings, 2014-2016.
  - Railroad Safety and Security Task Force - Meeting, 2014 May.
  - Railroad Safety and Security Task Force - Meeting, 2014 June 4.
  - Railroad Safety and Security Task Force - Meeting, 2014 Aug.
  - Railroad Safety and Security Task Force - Transportation Safety Board of Canada, 2014.
  - Railroad Safety and Security Task Force - Trespassing on Railroad Properties, 2015.
  - Railroad Safety and Security Task Force, 201.
  - Regional Resilience, 2016.
  - Regional Resilience, 2016.
  - Regional Resilience, 2016-2017.
  - Regional Resilience, 2016-2017.
  - Regional Resilience - Administration resilience efforts, 2017.
  - Regional Resilience - Dashboard Project, 2016 July.
  - Regional Resilience - Miscellaneous, undated.
  - Regional Resilience - Secure and Resilient Commonwealth Panel, 2017 Oct 19.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meetings, 2006-2007.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meetings, 2008 Jan-Apr.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meetings, 2008 June-July.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meetings, 2008 Oct.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meetings, 2008 Nov-Dec.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meetings, 2009.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meetings, 2010.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meetings, 2011.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meetings, 2012.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meetings, 2013.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meetings, 2014.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meeting, 2014 July 8.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meeting, 2014 Oct 21.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meetings, 2015.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Law Enforcement Technology Sub-panel, 2015 May 7.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meeting, 2015 May 21.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Law Enforcement Technology Sub-panel, 2015 Spet 15.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meeting, 2015 Nov 19.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meeting, 2016 June 1.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meeting, 2016 July 13.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Cyber Security Sub-panel, 2016.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Meeting, 2017 Oct 19.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Cyber Security Sub-panel, 2017 Dec 6.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Sign-in sheets, 2008-2015.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Strategic Plan (draft), 2009 Jan.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Strategic Plan, 2009 Jan.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Strategic Plan, 2009.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Strategic Framework (revision), 2015-2016.
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel - Sub-panels, 2007-2011.
  - Special Conservators of the Peace Task Force, 2014.
  - Special Conservators of the Peace Task Force - Agendas, 2014 June-Aug.
  - Special Conservators of the Peace Task Force - Meeting, 2014 June 25.
  - Special Conservators of the Peace Task Force - Meeting, 2014 July 24.
  - Special Conservators of the Peace Task Force - Meeting, 2014 Sept 29.
  - Special Conservators of the Peace Task Force - Program presentation, 2014 Oct 21.
  - Victim's Rights Coordinating Council, 2014 Mar 11.
  - Virginia Crisis Intervention Teams, 2014-2016.
  - Virginia Crisis Intervention Teams - Assessment site meeting, 2014 Oct 10.
  - Virginia Crisis Intervention Teams - Leadership Team Retreat, undated.
  - Virginia Crisis Intervention Teams - Substance Abuse and Mental Health Service Administration presentation, 2016 Mar 4.
  - Virginia Smart Communities Working Group, 2017 Oct.
- Series VI. Transition, XX., Extent: X cubic feet (X boxes). (Box X)
  - Secretary-elect, 2013-2014.
  - Transition Manual (Office of the Secretary, ABC, Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services Council), 2014.
  - Transition Manual (DCJS, DFS), 2014.
  - Transition Manual (DJJ, DMA), 2014.
  - Transition Manual (DOC), 2014.
  - Transition Manual (VDEM, DFP), 2014.
  - Transition Manual (VSP), 2014.
  - Status Reports (ABC, DOC), 2013.
  - Status Reports (DCJS, VDEM), 2013.
  - Status Reports (DFP, DFS, DJJ), 2013.
  - Status Reports (DMA, VPS, VSP), 2013.
- Series VI. Weekly Reports, XX., Extent: X cubic feet (X boxes). (Box X)
  - Agency weekly reports - ABC, 2014 May 23.
  - Agency weekly reports - ABC, 2015 Jan-Feb.
  - Agency weekly reports - ABC, 2016 Apr-July.
  - Agency weekly reports - ABC, 2016 Aug-Dec.
  - Agency weekly reports - ABC, 2017 Jan.
  - Agency weekly reports - Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services Council, 2016 May-2017 Jan.
  - Agency weekly reports - DOC, 2016 Apr-2017 Jan.
  - Agency weekly reports - DCJS, 2014 May 19; 2015 Jan-Mar.
  - Agency weekly reports - DCJS, 2016 Apr-June.
  - Agency weekly reports - DCJS, 2016 July-2017 Jan.
  - Agency weekly reports - VDEM, 2015 June 15; 2016 May-2017 Jan.
  - Agency weekly reports - DFP, 2015 June 8; 2016 Apr-2017 Jan.
  - Agency weekly reports - DFS, 2014 May 23; 2015 Jan-Feb.
  - Agency weekly reports - DFS, 2016 Apr-2017 Jan.
  - Agency weekly reports - Homeland Security and Resilience Staff Group, 2016 May-July.
  - Agency weekly reports - DJJ, 2014 May 27; 2015 Jan-Mar.
  - Agency weekly reports - DJJ, 2016 May-2017 Jan.
  - Agency weekly reports - DMA, 2016 May-2017 Jan.
  - Agency weekly reports - VSP, 2016 Apr-July.
  - Agency weekly reports - VSP, 2016 Aug-2017 Jan.
  - Office of the Secretary, 2016 June-2017 Jan.
  - Weekly reports to the Governor, 2014 May-2015 Mar.
  - Weekly reports to the Governor, 2016 Apr-May.
  - Weekly reports to the Governor, 2016 June-July.
  - Weekly reports to the Governor, 2016 Aug-2017 Jan.